Guide to the Craig Wirth broadcast journalism audio-visual collection 1903-1990s, bulk 1950s-1990s
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- 1998 donation
  - (Box 16)
    - CBS News: Moab dump story, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 332)
    - Blue Angels story, 1979; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 333)
    - Venice Beach, California, 1984; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 334)
    - Last flight of Western Airlines, 1987; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 335-336)
    - Film used in Holiday story, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 337)
    - 27 million-dollar house in Los Angeles; Mother's Day, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 338)
    - Country Craig; Mormons to Brazil, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 339)
    - Human train whistle; Grand Central Station, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 340)
    - Pan-Pacific Auditorium, Art Reed, Mormon architecture, 1986; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 341)
    - Apollo Theatre and Nicholas Brothers, 1983; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 342)
    - KCBS: Horse wedding, 1987; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 343)
  - (Box 17)
    - Star Trek 25th anniversary tape, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 344)
    - World of Wizards with Randy "the De-Bunker" Ransom, New Jersey, 1983; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 345)
    - Max Headroom material, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 346)
    - "Tapes of Wrath", undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 347)
    - KCBS tour, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 348-349)
    - Roy Rogers in Spanish, 1988; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 350)
    - Los Angeles earchquake, 1987; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 351)
    - Dodger Blue master, Los Angeles, California, 1989; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 352)
    - Possible "Subway Series" Yankees/Mets, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 353)
      New York Yankess and Mets baseball teams may compete in World Series
    - Raw footage of Catalina Island, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 354)
    - Train hobo: "Panhandle Jack;" Spinakers drill team, 1978; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 355)
    - Everly Brothers, 1986; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 356)
    - Take Two Clio winners, 1978; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 357)
  - (Box 18)
    - VIS News, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 358-368)
    - Getting Around, 1975; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 369)
      Masters thesis
    - Young and the Restless actual tapes, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 370)
    - CBS Early Morning, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 371)
    - Firefighters, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 372)
    - Homes series dub, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 373)
  - (Box 19)
    - Take Two: Clio Awards, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 374-375)
    - Full FNN sports stories, 1990; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 376-384)
    - Wirth wins 3 Emmys, 1985; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 385)
  - (Box 20)
    - KCBS: Bota, 1987; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 386)
    - FNN sports day footage, 1990; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 387-397)
    - Wirth acting debut as Mr. Landcaster on CBS Young and the Restless, 1987; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 398)
    - Political advertisements, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 399)
  - (Box 21)
    - FNN sports, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 400-408)
    - KHS: Nude drinking story, 1988; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 409)
  - (Box 22)
    - Good Year Blimp, 1989; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 410-411)
    - Dr. Pharmiory, professor of physics, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 412)
    - Brazil with Mormon Tabernacle Choir, 1981; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 413)
    - KCBS: Raw footage of Laird Studios, 1987; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 414)
    - KHJ souvenirs, Descanso Gardens, bombers, 1989; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 415)
    - Van Halen and Rodney Dangerfield promos, 1984; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 416)
    - WOR: National Press Photographers Association contest tape, 1984; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 417)
    - KCBS sports audition tape, 1987; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 418)
    - Clue VCR game, 1985; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 419)
    - Clowns, 1976; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 420)
    - KHJ Los Angeles: Wirth stories, 1989; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 421)
    - KTVX: Neon signwork, 1988; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 422)
    - KHJ Los Angeles: Mick League baseball, 1989; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 423)
  - (Box 23)
    - Travel Channel: Gettysburg raw footage, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 424-427)
    - KUTV stories, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 428-440)
  - (Box 24)
    - Drive in, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 441)
    - Centennial road tour, 1995; VHS videocassette (Cassette 442-444)
    - Bowling, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 445)
    - Interview with bomb worker, Wendover, Nevada; Enola Gay anniversary, Fat Man and Little Boy, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 446)
    - Old steam fire engine master, Daughters or Utah Pioneers, Bountiful, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 447)
    - Craig Wirth mining photographs, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 448-449)
    - Car collection, Browning, Ogden, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 450)
    - 1950s music (audio only), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 451)
    - Grist Mill, Tooele County, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 452)
    - Cantenial Stu (sic), 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 453)
    - Fruit stand, 1989; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 454)
    - Commercials (30 seconds raw footage), undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 455-456)
    - Carbon, County, Utah road, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 457-459)
    - Southern Utah sand shots, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 460)
    - Salt Lake Trappers vs. Helena baseball game, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 461-463)
    - CNBC studios dub, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 464)
  - (Box 25)
    - Everglades footage, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 465)
    - USA: Up all night with Rhonda Shear, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 466-468)
    - FNN Smokey Mountains, Tennesee, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 469-471)
    - Oscar history, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 472-473)
    - Bob Stupak and Stratosphere Casino, Las Vegas, Nevada, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 474-475)
    - City walk, urban design, Los Angeles, California., undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 476-477)
    - News boys in Los Angeles, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 478-479)
    - Russian defectors; First American 4th of July, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 480-481)
    - On the Map: Miami, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 482)
    - Sandwich contest, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 183)
    - Imperial Palace car collection, Las Vegas, Nevada, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 484)
    - Child actress Rachel Duncan, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 485)
    - Grand Hotel, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 486)
    - Bungalow home design, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 487-488)
    - Derks Field, Franklin Quest, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 489-490)
    - Trappers baseball story, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 491)
    - Photographs production material, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 492)
    - Private train cars, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 493)
    - Fruit stands on Highway 89, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 494)
    - Como Hot Springs, Morgan, Utah, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 495)
    - Beajolais arrives on Air France, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 496)
    - Porpoise story, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 497)
  - (Box 26)
    - Disneyland reference tapes, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 498-508)
    - Helper, Utah stories, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 509-520)
    - Beaver, Utah car show, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 521-534)
    - Carribean underwater footage, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 535-538)
    - Last silent movie organist, Gaylord Carter, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 539-545)
    - Beverly Hills hotel, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 546-550)
    - Treasure Island Casino, Las Vegas, Nevada, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 551-552)
  - (Box 27)
    - Travel business, 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 553)
    - Auto trends, vector 1 and 2 interview, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 554-555)
    - Chevrolet at Auto Show: 3-5, 1993; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 556-558)
    - Day spas (long), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 559)
    - Beaver courthouse, Hudson, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 560)
    - Eco expo, 1; Sims Noble, 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 551)
    - Car Names 2, 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 552)
      Logo, A and B-roll and standups, CNBC parking lot
    - Gangstar 1-2, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 553-554)
    - Long Beach Grand Prix, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 555)
    - Limo, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 556-557)
    - Auto shop, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 558-559)
    - Brigham Young University, Utah; Ned Alger, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 560)
    - Victrolia 1, 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 561-562)
    - Trains, Hudson 1, 2, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 563-564)
    - Old Salt Palace upper 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 565-566)
    - 100 year-olds, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 567)
    - Hilltop Café 3 of 3, 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 568)
    - Willie car, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 569)
    - Goshen Market 1, 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 570-571)
    - Don't waste Utah; Theron; girlfriend; Red Canyon; biker; Paradise Lost; pioneers, 1994; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 572)
    - Taxes 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 573)
    - McDonald's 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 574)
    - Firefighters steam 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 575)
    - Steam fire 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 576)
    - Dumb, stupid var show, Hudson Craig; Sun Bar, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 577)
    - JD Williams 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 578)
    - Governor's Mansion state 6, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 579)
    - KTVX: Nibley, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 580)
    - KTVX: Wirth canyon, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 581)
    - Car history, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 582)
    - Mine, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 583)
  - (Box 28)
    - Helper, Utah parade, Carbon County, Utah railroad, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 584-587)
    - MOS Interviews, A.K. David Sims Noble, 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 588)
    - On the Map: Glacier National Park, Montana, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 589)
    - Cruiser, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 590-593)
    - Hummer, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 594-595)
    - Promo, replacements, limited, Greensboro, North Carolina, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 596-597)
    - Graceland 5, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 598)
      Elvis in concert: "Burning Love," "Blue Suede Shoes"
    - DIC cartoon dub, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 599)
    - Recreational Equipment, Inc. (REI), Seattle, Washington, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 600)
    - Bugatti, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 601-602)
    - Gerber Food, Gerber babies, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 603)
    - Cadillac press preview, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 604-605)
      Ride and drive, B-roll stand-up, preview interviews, Jonathan Club
    - Car tips with Craig Wirth, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 606-607)
    - Car tips with Craig Wirth standups, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 608-609)
      Craig Wirth standups, mechanic tips with Bob
    - Hobby/model show 2-3: Craig Wirth and Sims, 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 610-611)
    - Civil War 1-3 (long), 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 612)
    - License plate, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 613)
    - Holland Lake Lodge 1, Holland Lake, Montana, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 614)
    - Parowan 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 615)
    - Architect 1, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 616)
    - 1960s and 1970s, State Street, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 617)
    - Feature reporter: GMA, KTVX, WWOR, KCBG, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 618)
    - American entrepreneur retrospective for FNN in Los Angeles, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 619)
  - (Box 29)
    - FNN story, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 620)
    - KTVS: Flamingo 1-2, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 621-622)
    - Famous footsteps slate, work tape, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 623-624)
    - Street machines unlimited, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 625)
    - Cinnabar show, 1990; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 626)
    - Hotel Newhouse implosion, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 627)
    - FNN: Tootsie roll advertisements, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 628)
    - CNBC: Airplane auction for news channel, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 629)
    - Christmas stuff, a split channel, 1993; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 630)
    - Magazine shoppe 1-2, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 631-632)
    - Awards night mixed audio, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 633)
    - Russia segment 1, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 634)
    - Berlin part four, final court, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 635)
    - Russia four show 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 636)
    - Russia show 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 637-639)
    - Rail, 1993-1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 640-646)
    - NBC: Gettysbugh last reunion tape, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 647)
    - Iwerks tapes 2-4, 1991; VHS videocassette (Cassette 648)
    - Graceland Enterprises, media B-roll, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 649)
    - B-17 and B-24 bombers in Europe, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 650)
    - Yellowstone fire, 1998; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 651)
    - Weapons juggler, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 652)
    - Venice 2, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 653)
    - Universal Studios, Hollywood Backdraft attraction and electronic press kit, 1989; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 654)
    - Hawaii 9, Polynesian center, Southern Utah highway scenes, 1980; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 655)
    - Pat Boone, 1995; VHS videocassette (Cassette 656)
    - Buster Keaton, 1995; VHS videocassette (Cassette 657)
    - Rachers clips, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 658)
    - Gymborie, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 659)
  - (Box 30)
    - Avalon standup, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 660)
    - Baseball Metros 3, Jose, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 661)
    - Dave Berg, Tonight Show, 1993; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 662)
    - Seattle fish market; Brummond, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 663)
    - Red Cross, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 664)
    - Dick Bass, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 665)
    - Computer 2 of 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 666)
    - Deweld beds 3; On the Map; Incline Plane; Johnstown, Pennsylvania, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 667)
    - Trax Nevada town, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 668)
    - Majestic Air; split channel, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 669)
    - Snowbird 6, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 670)
    - American Entertainment, retro (master, cut down versn), 1992; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 671)
    - Wendy's host, 1993; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 672)
    - Passion Fruit 3, 4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 673-674)
    - Nintendo 1, 3, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 675-676)
    - International American stories edited master, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 677)
    - For Real story: Rainforest, Los Angeles Bureau, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 679)
    - Oleg on Cam, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 680)
    - Racher 2, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 681)
    - Theme shop, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 682)
    - Eclipse 1, 3, Los Angeles, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 683-684)
    - Johnathon juggling 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 685)
    - High School farm 1-2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 686)
    - Cockroaches, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 687)
    - Craig Wirth standups, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 688)
    - B-25 bomber, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 689-691)
    - B-25, 1991; VHS videocassette (Cassette 692)
    - Salt mine - CNBC version, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 693)
    - KTVX: Airplane, Saltair, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 694)
    - Park City, Utah, Sushi 2, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 695-624)
    - KCBS Los Angeles: Movie shoot 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 625)
    - Hypnotist (dubbed twice), 1993; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 626)
    - Graceland, Memphis, Tennessee 1, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 627)
  - (Box 31)
    - CNBC Los Angeles: Wine 4, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 628)
    - KTVX: Pull tab, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 629-633)
    - 3D image, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 634-639)
    - KTVX: Zoo, 1992-1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 640-641)
    - Sandcastle2, 3, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 642-643)
    - KTVX: Back to school, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 644-645)
    - KTVX: Sears, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 646-647)
    - KTVX: Flamingos, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 648)
    - KTVX: Vault 1-3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 649-653)
    - KTVX: Mine 1, 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 654-657)
    - KTVX: Juggler, 1993; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 658-659)
    - CNBC: Ski show, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 660)
    - KTVX: Ribs 1, 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 661-662)
    - KTVX: Fair space, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 663-693)
    - CNBC Los Angeles: U.S.S. Missouri, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 694-696)
    - KTVX: Goal gall, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 697-698)
    - Still frame, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 699-700)
    - Beaujalais Houveav, British Airways cargo, 1993; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 701-702)
    - Darts 1-2, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 703-704)
    - KTVX: Modern Display 1, 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 705-706)
    - Giraffe 2, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 707)
    - Silver City press, Silvercity, New Mexico 4, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 708)
    - Rhonda up all night, introductions, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 709)
    - Lionel, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 710)
    - CNBC: Triumph 1; Sims, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 711)
    - KTVX: Food taste, Hudson, 1993; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 712)
    - CNBC: High School farm, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 713-714)
  - (Box 32)
    - KTVX: License Plate 2, 3, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 715)
    - KTVX: Monks 4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 716)
    - Old airport, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 717)
    - KTVX: Sample of story styles, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 718)
    - KTVX: Over the years, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 719-728)
    - Famous Footsteps: George Washington, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 729)
    - Famous Footsteps: CNBC music, Time Square studios, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 730)
    - Montgomery Area Chamber of Commerce; Diamond Film and Video Production, 1995; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 731)
    - CNBC: Adams 2, 1993; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 732)
    - CNBC Times Square re-enactment segment 6, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 733)
    - Famous Footsteps: Maps, titles, dissolves and logos, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 734)
    - TTC closing card, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 735)
    - KTVX: Derks Field torn down, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 746)
    - KTVX: 5 Points, 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 747)
    - Wirth co pupper, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 748)
    - KTVX: Tooele open; Mill tape 5, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 749)
    - McDonald's tape, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 750)
    - KTVX: Toys, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 751)
    - Paul Revere's ride: Mix channels, no Dolby, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 752)
    - CNBC: Today's stuff, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 753)
  - (Box 33)
    - Famous Footsteps: Gettysburg 1-10, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 754-763)
    - KTVX: Baseball, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 764-775)
    - Aquarium, Las Vegas, Nevada 1-4, 1989; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 776-779)
    - Wisconsin Dells, Wisconsin, Tommy Bartlet, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 780-781)
    - Bluejays, Toronto, Canada, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 782-788)
    - Bowling, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 789)
    - Blacksmith promo teaser, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 790-791)
  - (Box 34)
    - Stuart Edwards, 1997; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 792-796)
    - Invention convention 2, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 797)
    - CNBC: The Oaks Spa, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 798)
    - CNBC: Adventure convention 1, 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 799)
    - Old worker 1-3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 800)
    - Steam engine piece, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 801-802)
    - CNBC: Wendy's host 2, 1993; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 803)
    - CNBC: Big Rock 1, 7, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 804-805)
    - CNBC: Rock of fame, rock walk 1, 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 806)
    - Motorcycle 1-3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 807-809)
    - Purina pets 2, 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 810)
    - CNBC: Hotel suite, tourism 2, 3, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 811-813)
    - CNBC: Baseball photos, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 814)
    - KTVX: Kanab movies 6, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 815)
    - Kid book annual report, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 816)
    - Marie 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 817)
    - CNBC: Chevrolet at Chasen's, cocktails presentation, cars, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 818)
    - CNBC: Center dub, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 819)
    - CNBC: Motor trend 1, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 820)
    - Hill top 2, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 821)
    - CNBC: Super Bowl 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 822)
    - CNBC: Billboard, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 823-824)
    - KTVX: Yodel 1-2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 825-826)
    - KTVX: Billboard hanging, 1993; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 827)
    - Antelope Island 1-4, 1992-1993; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 828-832)
  - (Box 35)
    - Sanders 1-4, 1993; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 833-836)
    - Snowbird 1, 3, 5, 6, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 837-840)
    - Tractor 1-2, 1993; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 841-842)